Guide to the Dorothy Norman Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 1991 Acquisition, 1903-1989; 3; 33.08; 29 boxes
  - Articles on Alfred Stieglitz, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Early manuscripts, undated; 7 (Box 109)
  - Contact sheet - W. Mack, undated (Box 109)
  - Handwriting samples, 1928-1941, undated; 2 (Box 109)
  - Alfred Stieglitz correspondence, transcripts, undated; 2 (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Manuscript pages, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Parables, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Conversations, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz & Gandhi, undated (Box 109)
  - Stieglitz - Technical material, undated; 3 (Box 109)
  - Unsorted correspondence, 1930-1968; 22 (Box 110)
  - Brett, Dorothy, correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 110)
  - Dorothy Norman - Personal File, 1973 (Box 110)
  - Introduction of unidentified work, 1965 (Box 110)
  - Letter from Agnes Meyer to the New York Times, 1915 October 25, undated (Box 111)
  - Camera Work, undated (Box 111)
  - Steichen letters with complete typed copies, undated (Box 111)
  - Correspondence relating to India, 1955-1963 (Box 111)
  - Stieglitz and an American Place, undated (Box 111)
  - America and Alfred Stieglitz, undated (Box 111)
  - Alfred Stieglitz - American Seer, undated (Box 111)
  - Unsorted writings, undated; 19 (Box 111)
  - Unsorted writings, undated; 20 (Box 112)
  - Unsorted writings, undated; 4 (Box 113)
  - Fund for An American Place, pledge forms, 1932 (Box 113)
  - Dualities, subscription form, undated (Box 113)
  - Photograph of birch tree and branches, 1934 (Box 113)
  - Unsorted third-party correspondence, undated (Box 113)
  - Coburn, Alvin L., correspondence, 1951-1953, undated (Box 113)
  - Coomaraswamy, Ananda K., correspondence, 1923-1929 (Box 113)
  - Unsorted Alfred Stieglitz correspondence, transcripts and photostats, undated; 17 (Box 113)
  - Unsorted Alfred Stieglitz correspondence, transcripts and photostats, 1915-1930; 20 (Box 114)
  - Zayas, Marius de, and Virginia, correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 115)
  - Wedell, Lida von, correspondence, 1952-1953, undated (Box 115)
  - Alfred Stieglitz, handwriting samples, 1930-1941 (Box 115)
  - Taddei, Ezio. The Tresca Case, 1943 (Box 115)
  - Zayas, Marius de. When, How and Why Modern Art Came to New York, circa 1950 (Box 115)
  - Letters from Arthur Dove and Marsden Hartley to Paul Rosenfeld, undated (Box 115)
  - Unsorted writings, undated (Box 115)
  - Ross, Cary. "Stieglitz and the Art Dealers," and poems, undated (Box 115)
  - Haines, Robert E. "Alfred Stieglitz and the New Order of Consciousness in American Literature", 1971 April (Box 115)
  - Thomas, F. Richard. The Literary Admirers of Alfred Stieglitz, dissertation, 1970 (Box 115)
  - Printed material, undated (Box 115)
  - America and Alfred Stieglitz, dust jackets, 1934 (Box 115)
  - Buffalo exhibition, list of pictures, circa 1915 (Box 115)
  - Transcripts and photostats of Stieglitz correspondence
    - Adams, Ansel, undated (Box 115)
    - Annan, J. Craig (James Craig), undated (Box 115)
    - Benson, E., undated (Box 115)
    - Bragdon, Claude, undated (Box 115)
    - Brett, Dorothy, undated (Box 115)
    - Clurman, Harold, undated (Box 115)
    - Crane, Hart, undated (Box 115)
    - Demuth, Charles, undated (Box 115)
    - Dove, Arthur, undated; 3 (Box 115)
    - Emerson, P. H., undated (Box 115)
    - Enters, Angna, undated (Box 115)
    - Frank, Waldo, undated; 5 (Box 116)
    - Hermann, Sime, undated (Box 116)
    - Johnston, Dudley, undated (Box 116)
    - Kuehn, Heinrich, undated (Box 116)
    - Lawrence, D. H. (David Herbert), undated (Box 116)
    - Mumford, Lewis, undated (Box 116)
    - Norman, Nancy, undated (Box 116)
    - Phillips, Duncan, undated; 5 (Box 116)
    - Porter, Eliot, undated (Box 116)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul, undated; 2 (Box 116)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J. (Herbert Jacob), undated; 5 (Box 116)
    - Seligmann, Herbert J. (Herbert Jacob), undated; 5 (Box 117)
    - Stecker, Louis, undated (Box 117)
    - Steichen, Edward, undated; 6 (Box 117)
    - Stieglitz, Julius & Hannah, Flora & Leopold, undated (Box 117)
    - Strand, Rebecca, undated; 3 (Box 117)
    - Weston, Edward, undated (Box 117)
    - Wright, MacDonald (Stanton MacDonald-Wright), undated; 2 (Box 117)
    - Zayas, Marius de, undated; 2 (Box 118)
    - Zoler, Emil, undated; 3 (Box 118)
  - Dorothy Norman correspondence
    - Brett, Dorothy, 1929-1933 (Box 118)
    - Fraprie, F. R., 1947-1949 (Box 118)
    - James, Rebecca Salsbury, 1946-1947 (Box 118)
    - Karpel, Bernard, 1947 (Box 118)
    - Parker, William, 1970 (Box 118)
    - Strauss, Flora, 1967, undated (Box 118)
    - Taylor, Elita, 1965 (Box 118)
    - Yale University, 1947-1973 (Box 118)
    - Unsorted correspondence, 1934-1974; 4 (Box 118)
  - Photostat and transcript of Stieglitz autograph album (1884), undated (Box 118)
  - Bibliographies - Alfred Stieglitz, 1947 (Box 118)
  - Biographical notes on painters and photographers, undated (Box 118)
  - Biographical material and lists relating to Alfred Stieglitz, 1957, undated (Box 118)
  - Blurbs - Alfred Stieglitz, undated (Box 119)
  - New York Times - Stieglitz piece, undated (Box 119)
  - Stieglitz exhibits, notes, undated (Box 119)
  - Unsorted writings, undated (Box 119)
  - The Intimate Eye, exhibition, 1986 (Box 119)
  - Material at Yale, undated (Box 119)
  - Notes on Stieglitz, undated (Box 119)
  - Other museums (press releases), 1940-1970 (Box 119)
  - Parker notes, undated (Box 119)
  - Photostats from books, undated (Box 119)
  - Material relating to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; 2 (Box 119)
  - Alfred Stieglitz prints, for reproduction in book, undated (Box 119)
  - Quotes, 1964, undated (Box 119)
  - Alfred Stieglitz, research material, undated; 2 (Box 119)
  - Printed material, 1956-1984, undated; 2 (Box 119)
  - Alfred Stieglitz stories used in manuscript, undated (Box 119)
  - Unsorted writings, 1944-1987, undated; 4 (Box 119)
  - F. Richard Thomas, "Petition for Approval of PhD Thesis Topic", 1968 (Box 119)
  - Transcripts and photostats of unsorted Alfred Stieglitz correspondence, undated; 7 (Box 119)
  - Transcripts and photostats of Alfred Stieglitz correspondence
    - Anderson, Sherwood, undated; 3 (Box 120)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, undated (Box 120)
    - Hartley, Marsden, undated; 2 (Box 120)
    - Zayas, Marius de, undated; 4 (Box 120)
    - Unsorted correspondence, undated; 7 (Box 120)
    - Unsorted correspondence, undated; 5 (Box 121)
  - List of exhibitions, undated (Box 121)
  - List of missing plates, 1968, undated (Box 121)
  - Notes about Alfred Stieglitz material, 1960, undated (Box 121)
  - Alfred Stieglitz, biographical writings, undated (Box 121)
  - Unsorted writings, undated; 2 (Box 121)
  - Photography and painting, printed material, 1916-1945, undated; 5 (Box 121)
  - Book reviews, 1986-1989, undated (Box 121)
  - Book dummy with photo corners, undated (Box 121)
  - Alphabet stamps, undated (Box 121)
  - Printed material, circa 1927-1980 (Box 121)
  - Printed material, 1915-1949, undated (Box 122 (Oversize))
  - Printed material, 1913-1987; 5 (Box 123 (Oversize))
  - Proof sheets of printed photographs, undated (Box 124 (Oversize))
  - Stieglitz book pasteup, undated (Box 124 (Oversize))
  - Newspaper clippings and magazines, 1944-1959; 2 (Box 124 (Oversize))
- April 1997 Acquisition, 1908-1996; 4; 54.38; 55 boxes
  Organized under three headings: Correspondence and Subject Files, Personal and Professional Papers, and Scrapbooks.
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    Arranged in two alphabetical runs.
    - Photocopies of original box labels, undated (Box 125)
    - "A" General, circa 1947-1992; 4 (Box 125)
    - Abrahams, Edward, 1979 -1993 (Box 125)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1980-1982, undated (Box 125)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1956-1976, undated (Box 125)
      Includes April & May 1961 issues of Art Newsletter.
    - Amram, Marianna & Emilie, 1959-1976, undated (Box 125)
    - Andrews, Stephen (& Cyril Frankel), 1962-1976, undated (Box 125)
    - Apostolos-Cappadona, Diane, 1980-1995, undated; 2 (Box 125)
      Includes essays on various topics by Diane Apostolos-Cappadona.
    - Archives of American Art, 1960-1967 (Box 125)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish & Christa, 1958-1972, undated (Box 125)
    - Asia Society, 1969-1972, undated (Box 125)
    - "B" General, 1952-1997, undated; 3 (Box 125)
    - Bakst (empty folder), undated (Box 125)
    - Barnes, Albert C., 1926-1991, undated (Box 125)
    - Barr, Alfred H., Jr., 1967-1973 (Box 125)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1989-1990 (Box 125)
    - Borg, John & Francis, 1936-1975, undated (Box 125)
    - Bose, Buddhadeva, 1952-1963 (Box 125)
    - Brady, Roberto, 1972-1976 (Box 125)
    - Brett, Dorothy, 1931-1971; 2 (Box 126)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1937-1942 (Box 126)
    - Bry, Doris, 1947-1972 (Box 126)
    - Bunnen, Lucinda, 1972-1974 (Box 126)
    - "C" General, 1970-1983, undated; 4 (Box 126)
    - Cage, John, 1977-1987 (Box 126)
    - Camfield, William, 1969-1970 (Box 126)
    - Campbell, Joseph & Erdman, Jean, 1935-1975, undated (Box 126)
    - Carlton, Margaret & Winslow, 1964-1976, undated (Box 126)
    - Cathedral of St. John the Divine (New York, N.Y.), 1973-1987 (Box 126)
    - C. G. Jung-Institut (Zurich, Switzerland), 1964, undated (Box 126)
    - Chakravarty, Amiya, 1975-1976 (Box 126)
    - Chalidze, Vera, 1973-1974 (Box 126)
    - Cirker, Howard, 1976 (Box 126)
    - Cohen, Arthur & Elaine, 1975-1976 (Box 126)
    - Constable, Rosalind, 1967-1975, undated (Box 126)
    - Cooper, Muriel, 1965-1972, undated (Box 126)
    - Crownover, David, 1973 (Box 126)
    - "D" General, circa 1963-1976; 5 (Box 126)
    - Daubney, James, 1988 February 16 (Box 126)
    - De Fanti, Charles, 1973-1975 (Box 126)
    - Dijkstra, Bram, 1965-1971, undated (Box 126)
    - Dorr, Nell, 1965-1973, undated (Box 126)
    - Dowd, Janet, 1959-1975 (Box 126)
    - Dragon, Edward F., 1964-1976, undated (Box 126)
    - Duell, Charles & Ruth, 1950-1973, undated (Box 126)
    - "E" General, circa 1960-1992; 3 (Box 127)
    - Embree, Ainslie Thomas, 1963-1970, undated (Box 127)
    - Enters, Angna, undated (Box 127)
    - Ettinghausen, Richard, 1976 (Box 127)
    - EH Magazine, 1956, undated (Box 127)
    - "F" General, 1974-1995, undated; 2 (Box 127)
    - Feibleman, Jimmy, 1937-1938; 12 (Box 127)
    - Frick Collection, 1971 (Box 127)
    - "G" General, 1964-1976; 2 (Box 128)
    - George Eastman House, 1974-1975, undated (Box 128)
    - Gerard, A., 1945 (Box 128)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1962-1988, undated; 3 (Box 128)
    - Graves, Morris, 1958-1981; 3 (Box 128)
    - Graves, Wallace, 1975 (Box 128)
    - Gray, Cleve, 1967-1976, undtated (Box 128)
    - Guild Hall of East Hampton, 1968-1994, undated (Box 128)
    - Gwinn, Fred, 1954-1975, undated (Box 128)
    - "H" General, circa 1957-1996; 4 (Box 128)
    - Haines, Robert, 1969-1976 (Box 128)
    - Hasselriis, Mark, 1958-1982, undated (Box 128)
    - Hertzberg, Sidney, 1978, undated (Box 128)
    - Holborn, Mark, 1978-1991, undated (Box 128)
    - Homer, William Innes, 1970-1976 (Box 128)
    - "I" General, 1964-1976 (Box 128)
    - Illich, Ivan, 1972-1976 (Box 128)
    - "J" General, 1977-1994, undated; 2 (Box 129)
    - Jacobs, William K., Jr., 1978-1991, undated (Box 129)
    - Jayakar, Pupul, 1952-1964, undated; 2 (Box 129)
    - Jones, Harold, 1975-1976, undated (Box 129)
    - Josephy, Robert, 1925-1937, undated; 10 (Box 129)
    - "K" General, 1964-1976, undated; 2 (Box 129)
    - Kirschbaum, Anne, 1953-1974, undated (Box 129)
    - Kramrisch, Stella, 1950-1993, undated; 4 (Box 130)
    - Kreisky, Bruno, 1959-1962, undated (Box 130)
    - "L " General, 1955-1995, undated; 3 (Box 130)
    - Lash, Trude W., 1972-1993, undated (Box 130)
    - Lowe, Sue Davidson, 1983-1989 (Box 130)
    - "M" General, 1970-1976, undated; 3 (Box 130)
    - Maguire, William, 1977-1991 (Box 130)
    - Marin, John, 1905-1984, undated; 4 (Box 130)
    - May, Rollo, 1938-1975, undated (Box 130)
    - McCarthy, Eugene & O'Dwyer, Paul, 1968-1973 (Box 130)
    - Morgan, Ann, 1971 (Box 130)
    - Moynihan, Daniel, 1973-1975 (Box 130)
    - Mumford, Lewis, 1946-1990, undated; 2 (Box 130)
    - Museum of African Art (U.S.), 1971-1974 (Box 130)
    - Musil, Robert, 1938-1939 (Box 130)
    - "N" General, circa 1963-1976; 3 (Box 131)
    - Narasimhan, C. V. (Chakravarthi V.), 1957-1973 (Box 131)
    - Nehru, Jawaharlal, 1938-1964; 2 (Box 131)
    - Newhall, Beaumont, 1975, undated (Box 131)
    - New York (N.Y.) Board of Elections, undated (Box 131)
    - New York Office, 1946-1990, undated; 2 (Box 131)
    - The New York Times, 1968-1971 (Box 131)
    - Nin, Anaïs, 1937-1979, undated; 5 (Box 131)
    - Nivola, Constantino & Ruth, 1930-1989; 2 (Box 131)
    - Norman Foundation, 1976-1994 (Box 131)
    - "O" General, 1955-1995, undated (Box 131)
    - Odets, Clifford, 1946-1954 (Box 131)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia & Bry, Doris, 1931-1950; 3 (Box 131)
    - O'Keeffe, John, 1976 (Box 131)
    - "P" General, 1955-1995, undated; 2 (Box 131)
    - Palkhivala, N. A. (Nani Ardeshir), 1977-1993 (Box 131)
    - Pandit, Nan, undated (Box 131)
    - Pearl Wong, Inc., 1967-1976 (Box 131)
    - Photography, 1953, undated (Box 131)
    - Picabia, Francis, 1954 (Box 131)
    - "Q" General, 1984-1990 (Box 132)
    - "R" General, 1975-1993, undated; 3 (Box 132)
    - Rainer, Luise, 1958-1962 (Box 132)
    - Rambova, Natacha, undated (Box 132)
    - Raja Singam, S. Durai, 1972-1975 (Box 132)
    - Rao, Shanta, 1975 (Box 132)
    - Rawls, Eugenia, 1966 (Box 132)
    - Reich, Charles, 1970-1971 (Box 132)
    - Reich, Sheldon, 1963-1971 (Box 132)
    - Reis, Claire, 1957-1976 (Box 133)
    - Riesman, David, 1970, 1976 (Box 133)
    - Rockefeller, John D. III (John Davison), 1964 (Box 133)
    - Rosenberg, Harold, 1975, undated (Box 133)
    - Rosenfeld, Isadore, 1971-1976 (Box 133)
    - Rothschild, Alix, baroness de, 1969-1974 (Box 133)
    - Roy, S. K., 1975-1976 (Box 133)
    - "S" General, 1957-1992; 4 (Box 133)
    - Sahgal, Gautam & Tara, 1958-1976 (Box 133)
    - Sarabhai, Gautam & Gira, 1964-1976, undated (Box 133)
    - Schiff, Dorothy, 1972-1976 (Box 133)
    - Schubert, Dorothy, 1968-1976, undated (Box 133)
    - Seldes, Marian, 1936-1976 (Box 133)
    - Seligman, Eustace, 1958-1976, undated (Box 133)
    - Sherbert, Paul C., 1961-1971, undated (Box 133)
    - Siembab, Carl, 1964-1976 (Box 133)
    - Singh, Madanjeet, 1958-1968, undated (Box 133)
    - Singh, Nirmal, 1967-1972 (Box 133)
    - Smith, Lillian, 1949-1972, undated (Box 133)
    - Snyder, Robert, 1970 (Box 133)
    - SONA, 1965-1973, undated (Box 133)
    - Spaeth, Otto, 1966-1970 (Box 133)
    - Stecker, Dora, 1964-1976, undated (Box 133)
    - Stecker, Robert & Beth, 1959-1975, undated (Box 134)
    - Steichen, Edward, 1973 (Box 134)
    - Stein, Gertrude & Toklas, Alice B., 1937-1947, undated (Box 134)
    - Stieglitz, James E., 1918 (Box 134)
    - Straton, Dora, 1968-1975 (Box 134)
    - Straus, Flora, 1967-1974, undated (Box 134)
    - Straus, Roger William, Jr., 1961-1975, undated (Box 134)
    - Syracuse University, 1964-1968 (Box 134)
    - Syracuse University Press, 1964-1967 (Box 134)
    - "T" General, 1981-1982, undated; 3 (Box 134)
    - Thant, U, 1965, 1972 (Box 134)
    - Thomas, Richard, 1968-1971 (Box 134)
    - Thompson, Bill, 1973-1974, undated (Box 134)
    - Tillich, Hannah, 1937-1975, undated; 2 (Box 134)
    - Tishman, Ruth & Paul, 1972-1975, undated (Box 134)
    - Tomkins, Calvin & Judy, 1930-1976 (Box 134)
    - Trager, Frank, 1964-1968 (Box 134)
    - Trocmé, Pat & Jean, 1967-1973, undated (Box 134)
    - Turner, Evan H., 1970-1976, undated (Box 134)
    - "U" General, 1982-1985; 2 (Box 134)
    - "V" General, 1966-1994, undated; 2 (Box 134)
    - Van Löben Sels, Robin E., 1975-1976, undated (Box 134)
    - Van Nostrand, Dorothy, 1968-1974 (Box 134)
    - Varèse, Edgard, 1965-1972, undated (Box 134)
    - Vreeland, Betty & Tompkins, Peter, 1976, undated (Box 134)
    - "W" General, 1951-1995, undated; 2 (Box 134)
    - Walsh, Richard J., Jr., 1965-1971, undated (Box 135)
    - Weil, Frank & Denie, 1971-1976, undated (Box 135)
    - Weis, Elinor, 1964, undated (Box 135)
    - White, Minor, 1967-1971, undated (Box 135)
    - Wiener, Ingeborg, 1968-1976, undated (Box 135)
    - Wight, Frederick, 1958-1972, undated (Box 135)
    - Wilder, Catherine, 1976 (Box 135)
    - Willeford, William, 1964-1969 (Box 135)
    - Wolf, Howard, 1972-1975, undated (Box 135)
    - Wright, Helen, 1968-1972, undated (Box 135)
    - Wright, Richard, 1964-1965 (Box 135)
    - Wu, Nancy, 1986-1994 (Box 135)
    - Winston, Lydia K., 1938 (Box 135)
    - "XYZ" General, 1975-1993 (Box 135)
    - "Y" General, 1958-1974, undated (Box 135)
    - Young, Nancy Ross, 1961-1975 (Box 135)
    - "Z" General, 1963-1974, undated (Box 135)
    - Zigrosser, Carl, 1968-1972, undated (Box 135)
    - Adams, Ansel, 1949-1985, undated; 3 (Box 136)
    - An American Place Fund, undated (Box 136)
    - Anderson, Sherwood, 1946-1948, undated; 2 (Box 136)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1947-1965 (Box 136)
    - Baldwin, Roger, 1937-1948; 2 (Box 136)
    - Barnes, Albert C., 1947-1957, undated; 3 (Box 136)
    - Barr, Alfred, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Bauer, C., 1977-1981 (Box 136)
    - Beard, Mary, 1936?-1979 (Box 136)
    - Beecher, John, 1947-1974; 2 (Box 136)
      Includes signed copy of "Their Blood Cries Out."
    - Bhagat, Usha, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Blackley, J. B., 1964, undated (Box 136)
    - Bloch, Ernst, 1946-1947; 3 (Box 136)
    - Borgese, Giuseppe Antonio, 1946 (Box 136)
    - Boulanger, Nadia, 1939-1941, undated (Box 136)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1951-1969; 2 (Box 136)
    - Boyle, Kay, 1949-1954 (Box 136)
    - Bragdon, Henry W. & Claude, 1946-1947 (Box 136)
    - Braziller, George, 1965 (Box 136)
    - Brecht, Bertolt, 1946-1971; 2 (Box 136)
    - Breit, Harvey, 1940? (Box 136)
    - Brett, Dorothy, 1932-1974, undated; 7 (Box 136)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1938-1946, undated; 2 (Box 136)
    - Brown, John, 1950-1955; 2 (Box 136)
    - Buck, Pearl S. (Pearl Sydenstricker), 1959-1965, undated (Box 136)
    - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1956-1962 (Box 136)
    - Burland, C. A. (Cottie Arthur), 1960-1962 (Box 136)
    - Burnier, Raymond, 1950-1954 (Box 136)
    - Burton, Virginia, 1967-1986, undated (Box 136)
    - "C" General, 1935-1969, undated (Box 136)
    - Cage, John, 1955-1956; 3 (Box 136)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1952 (Box 136)
    - Camus, Albert, 1947-1948; 3 (Box 136)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin N. (Benjamin Nathan), 1937, undated; 3 (Box 136)
    - Cartier-Bresson, Henri, circa 1948-1959; 2 (Box 136)
    - Cato, Robert, 1958-1969, undated (Box 136)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1965 (Box 136)
    - Clurman, Harold, 1929-1958; 3 (Box 136)
    - Constable, Rosalind, 1954-1964, undated; 2 (Box 136)
    - Coomaraswamy, Ananda K. (Ananda Kentish), 1932-1969, undated; 5 (Box 136)
    - Cooney, James P., 1940 (Box 136)
    - Cooper, J. S., 1956 (Box 136)
    - Cooper, Loraine, 1955-1965, undated (Box 136)
    - Crishna, Amie, 1959-1960, undated (Box 137)
    - Crosby, Caresse, 1956-1968 (Box 137)
    - Crowley, Alice, 1958, undated (Box 137)
    - Dahlberg, Edward, 1937-1938; 2 (Box 137)
    - D'Amico, Victor, 1960-1970 (Box 137)
    - Dayal - Schlesinger, 1962-1969, undated (Box 137)
    - DeFanti, Charles, 1974 (Box 137)
    - De Mazia, Violette, 1960 (Box 137)
    - Dorr, Nell, 1958-1962, undated (Box 137)
    - Dreiser, Theodore, 1937-1941; 2 (Box 137)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1947-1958; 3 (Box 137)
    - Durrell, Lawrence, 1937-1940, undated (Box 137)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1953-1955 (Box 137)
    - Elisofen, Eliot, 1955-1973, undated (Box 137)
    - Ellis, Havelock, 1937-1940 (Box 137)
    - Elmslie, George (empty folder), undated (Box 137)
    - Ensminger, Douglas, 1953-1954 (Box 137)
    - Enters, Angna, 1927-1963, undated; 2 (Box 137)
    - Ettinghausen, Richard, 1966-1967 (Box 137)
    - Everson, W. (empty folder), undated (Box 137)
    - Fabre, Michel, 1963 (Box 137)
    - Fairbanks, Margaret, 1929-1951 (Box 137)
    - Feibleman, James Kern, undated (Box 137)
    - Fischel, Marguerite, 1946-1949? (Box 137)
    - Fischer, Louis, 1917-1979, undated; 3 (Box 137)
    - Fisk University, 1949-1970 (Box 137)
    - Fitzsimmons, James, 1962 (Box 137)
    - Francken, Ruth, 1959, undated (Box 137)
    - Frank, Waldo, 1939-1960; 4 (Box 137)
    - Freeman, Joe, 1952-1957 (Box 137)
    - Freeman, Joseph, 1951-1957, undated; 3 (Box 137)
    - Fry, Christopher, 1940 (Box 137)
    - Fülöp-Miller, René, 1958-1960; 2 (Box 137)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1961-1966, undated; 2 (Box 137)
    - Gandhi, Devadas, 1950-1954; 2 (Box 137)
    - Gandhi, Rajiv, 1985 (Box 137)
    - Ghirshman, Roman, 1958 (Box 137)
    - Githens, 1994 September 23 (Box 137)
    - Goldman, Emma, undated (Box 137)
    - Goldwater, Bert, 1953-1957 (Box 137)
    - Goodwin, Philip Lippincott, 1921-1953; 4 (Box 137)
    - Goodyear, Rosalie, 1949 (Box 137)
    - Graham, Frank, 1951-1954; 2 (Box 137)
    - Graves, Morris, circa 1962-1974 (Box 137)
    - Gurewitsch, David, 1964-1973, undated (Box 137)
    - Hartley, M. (empty folder), undated (Box 137)
    - Hartmann, Bertram (empty folder), undated (Box 137)
    - Hasegawa, Saburō, 1952 (Box 137)
    - The Heroic Encounter, 1939-1980, undated; 3 (Box 137)
    - Hertzberg, Sidney, 1953-1965, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - Hillman, James, 1964 (Box 138)
    - Hoffman, Michael E., 1968-1973 (Box 138)
    - Holden, Arthur C. & Miriam, 1929, undated (Box 138)
    - Howard, Evelyn, 1937-1997, undated (Box 138)
    - Howland, Harold, 1952-1954, undated; 3 (Box 138)
    - Hussain, Azim, 1962, undated (Box 138)
    - Hutheesing, Krishna (empty folder), undated (Box 138)
    - "I" General, 1959-1964 (Box 138)
    - Illich, Ivan, 1974, undated (Box 138)
    - Isaacs, Lewis M., Jr., 1965 (Box 138)
    - Ittleson, Blanche, 1955 (Box 138)
    - Jacobi, Jolande, 1958-1973, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - Jacques, Denyse, 1958 (Box 138)
    - James, Oliver B., 1947 (Box 138)
    - Jaffé, Aniela, 1958, 1962 (Box 138)
    - Jayakar, Pupul, undated (Box 138)
    - Jayakar, Radhi, 1958-1965, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - John M. Watkins, publishers and booksellers, 1960 (Box 138)
    - Jones, Harold, undated (Box 138)
    - "K " General, 1937-1964, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - Kahler, Alice, 1974-1976, undated; 4 (Box 138)
    - Katju, G. N., 1950-1951, undated (Box 138)
    - Katz, Leo, 1951-1957, undated (Box 138)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1946 (Box 138)
    - Keehn, Thomas B., 1953-1957 (Box 138)
    - Keene, F. (empty folder), undated (Box 138)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1960-1961, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - Kintner, Jean, 1953-1959 (Box 138)
    - Klein, Alexander, 1950-1951 (Box 138)
    - Knapp, Elizabeth, 1951-1956 (Box 138)
    - Knauth, Anne, 1951, undated (Box 138)
    - Knittel, Luise Rainer, 1964-1976, undated (Box 138)
    - Koussevitsky, Olga, 1963-1971, undated (Box 138)
    - Koussevitzky, Serge, 1971 (Box 138)
    - Kramrisch, Stella, 1935-1981, undated (Box 138)
    - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Lawrence Schlesinger), 1957-1970; 2 (Box 138)
      Includes "The Forgotten Man of Education" and "Need for a New Subdiscipline in the Medical Profession."
    - Kunz, F. L., 1954 (Box 138)
    - "L" General, 1950-1964, undated; 2 (Box 138)
    - Lachaise, Isabelle, 1937-1947 (Box 138)
    - Lamb, Beatrice, 1940-1956, undated (Box 138)
    - Lanier, Jean, 1973-1976, undated (Box 138)
    - Lasalle, H., 1973 (Box 138)
    - Lash, Trude, 1951-1957, undated (Box 138)
    - Latzko, S. D., 1946, 1954 (Box 138)
    - Laughlin, Jay, 1939 (Box 138)
    - Lawrence, Frieda, 1937-1946; 2 (Box 138)
    - Lawrence, Margaret, 1947 (Box 138)
    - Layard, John, 1947-1962, undated; 2 (Box 138)